Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection, 63573
  - Composer: Bendix, Theodore Title: Grand American Fantasia. Tone Pictures of the North and South Uniform Title: Grand American Fantasia Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: 55725-52, undated; 31142040614482; 66665 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Composer: Bendix, William Title: A la Balerina Uniform Title: A la Balerina Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4374-21, undated; 31142040614482; 66664 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Composer: Bennet, C. W., arr. Title: National Melodies Uniform Title: National Melodies Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 13277-14, undated; 31142040613120; 66663 (Box 127, Folder 1855)
  - Composer: Bennett, William Sterndale, Sir Title: Die Mai-Konigin Uniform Title: May queen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2500, undated; 31142040613609; 66662 (Box 136, Folder 1911)
  - Composer: Bennett, William Sterndale, Sir Title: Die Mai-Konigin Uniform Title: May queen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2501, undated; 31142040613609; 66661 (Box 136, Folder 1912)
  - Composer: Bennett, William Sterndale, Sir Title: Die Mai-Konigin Uniform Title: May queen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2502, undated; 31142040613195; 66660 (Box 134, Folder 1895)
  - Composer: Bennett, William Sterndale, Sir Title: Die Mai-Konigin Uniform Title: May queen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2503, undated; 31142040613195; 66659 (Box 134, Folder 1894)
  - Composer: Berge, Irenee Title: Suite Orientale No. 2 Uniform Title: Suite Orientale No. 2. India; arr. Publisher information: New York: Ross Jungnickel Plate Number: 69-31, undated; 31142040614482; 66658 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Composer: Berge, Irenee Title: Suite Orientale No. 6 Uniform Title: Suite Orientale No. 6. China; arr. Publisher information: New York: Ross Jungnickel Plate Number: 73-44, undated; 31142040614482; 66657 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Composer: Berger, Rudolf Title: Amoureuse Uniform Title: Amoureuse; arr. Publisher information: Paris (France): Enoch et Cie. (E. Dupre [printer]) Plate Number: E. et C. 4691. Engraver: Gulon, undated; 31142040612874; 66656 (Box 102, Folder 1349)
  - Composer: Berger, Wilhelm Title: Die erwachte Rose Uniform Title: Erwachte Rose Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4357, undated; 31142040613500; 66655 (Box 146, Folder 2060)
  - Composer: Berlin, Irving Title: (I Wonder Why?) You're Just in Love Uniform Title: You're Just in Love Publisher information: New York: Irving Berlin Music Corporation, undated; 31142040613385; 66654 (Box 158, Folder 2534)
  - Composer: Berlin, Irving Title: A Pretty Girl Is Like a Melody Uniform Title: Pretty Girl Is Like a Melody Publisher information: New York: Irving Berlin Music Corporation, undated; 31142040613377; 66653 (Box 159, Folder 2547)
  - Composer: Berlin, Irving Title: Always Uniform Title: Always Publisher information: New York: Irving Berlin Music Company, undated; 31142040613518; 66652 (Box 145, Folder 2014)
  - Composer: Berlin, Irving Title: Bugle Song Uniform Title: Oh, how I hate to get up in the morning; arr. Publisher information: New York: Waterson Berlin and Snyder Co., undated; 31142040612940; 66651 (Box 109, Folder 1559)
  - Composer: Berlin, Irving Title: God Bless America Uniform Title: God Bless America Publisher information: New York: Irving Berlin Music Corporation, undated; 31142040613369; 66650 (Box 160, Folder 2586)
  - Composer: Berlin, Irving Title: Remember Uniform Title: Remember Publisher information: New York: Irving Berlin, Inc. Music Publishers, undated; 31142040613518; 66649 (Box 145, Folder 2009)
  - Composer: Berlin, Irving Title: White Christmas Uniform Title: White Christmas Publisher information: New York: Irving Berlin, undated; 31142040613211; 66648 (Box 175, Folder 3302)
  - Composer: Berlioz, Hector Title: Benvenuto Cellini. Ouverture. Op. 23 Uniform Title: Benvenuto Cellini. Ouverture. Op. 23 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.1139, undated; 31142040614482; 66647 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Composer: Berlioz, Hector Title: Fausts Verdamniss Uniform Title: Damnation de Faust, undated; 31142040613559; 66646 (Box 141, Folder 1967)
  - Composer: Berlioz, Hector Title: March Hongroise Uniform Title: Damnation de Faust. Hungarian March Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson and Co. Plate Number: 3p, undated; 31142040614482; 66645 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Composer: Berlioz, Hector Title: Marche Hongroise. From Damnation de Faust Uniform Title: Damnation de Faust. Hungarian March; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2742-35, undated; 31142040614482; 66644 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Composer: Berlioz, Hector Title: Romeo et Juliette Uniform Title: Romeo et Juliette Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 818 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613278; 66643 (Box 169, Folder 2964)
  - Composer: Berlioz, Hector Title: Romeo et Juliette Uniform Title: Romeo et Juliette Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 875 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613278; 66642 (Box 169, Folder 2965)
  - Composer: Berlioz, Hector Title: The Damnation of Faust. Scene II Uniform Title: Damnation de Faust. Scene II, undated; 31142040613047; 66641 (Box 119, Folder 1712)
  - Composer: Berlioz, Hector Title: The Damnation of Faust Uniform Title: Damnation de Faust Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 2376, undated; 31142040613559; 66640 (Box 141, Folder 1966)
  - Composer: Bernauer, Josef Title: Sang romischer Germanen-Sklaven Uniform Title: Sang romischer Germanen-Sklaven, undated; 31142040612882; 66639 (Box 103, Folder 1390)
  - Composer: Bernauer, Josef Title: Sang romischer Germanen-Sklaven Uniform Title: Sang romischer Germanen-Sklaven Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G.H. 4345 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613468; 66638 (Box 150, Folder 2189)
  - Composer: Bernstein, Leonard Title: West Side Story. Selections Uniform Title: West Side Story. Selections, undated; 31142040612924; 66637 (Box 107, Folder 1532)
  - Composer: Beschnitt, J. Title: 3 Lieder fur Mannerchor (Der Lethetrunk vom Rhein; Mein Schifflein Treib in Mitten; Hoffning) Uniform Title: 3 Lieder fur Mannerchor Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote and G. Bock Plate Number: B. and B.4699., undated; 31142040612627; 66636 (Box 77, Folder 988)
  - Composer: Beschnitt, J. Title: Die einsame Kiefer Uniform Title: Einsame Kiefer, undated; 31142040613013; 66635 (Box 116, Folder 1650)
  - Composer: Binet, Frederic Title: Le Retour des Gondoliers Uniform Title: Retour des Gondoliers Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 14865, undated; 31142040612908; 66634 (Box 105, Folder 1478)
  - Composer: Birseck, L. Title: Sonntag Uniform Title: Sonntag Publisher information: New York: Luckhardt and Belder Plate Number: L. and B. no. 1 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613260; 66633 (Box 170, Folder 2990)
  - Composer: Bishop, Henry Title: Home, sweet Home Uniform Title: Home, sweet Home; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 9113-3, undated; 31142040613435; 66632 (Box 153, Folder 2328)
  - Composer: Bishop, Thomas Brigham Title: Battle Hymn of the Republic Uniform Title: Battle Hymn of the Republic; arr. Plate Number: 29482-22, undated; 31142040613120; 66631 (Box 127, Folder 1852)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: Agnus Dei Uniform Title: Agnus Dei; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5591-46, undated; 31142040612791; 66630 (Box 94, Folder 1156)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: Carmen. March Uniform Title: Carmen. March; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4298-34, undated; 31142040612452; 66629 (Box 60, Folder 748)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: Carmen. Selection from Georges Bizet's Opera Uniform Title: Carmen. Selection; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4250-71, undated; 31142040614482; 66628 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: L'Arlesienne Suite, No. 1 Uniform Title: Arlesienne. Suite No. 1 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 26355, undated; 31142040614474; 66627 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: L'Arlesienne. Erste Orchestersuite Uniform Title: Arlesienne. Suite No. 1 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.1953., undated; 31142040614474; 66626 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: L'Arlesienne. Zweite Orchestersuite Uniform Title: Arlesienne. Suite No. 2 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.1804/5, undated; 31142040614474; 66625 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: L'Arlesienne. Zweite Orchestersuite Uniform Title: Arlesienne. Suite No. 2 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.1954., undated; 31142040614474; 66624 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: Petit Mari, Petite Femme from Suite d'Orchestra, Op. 22 Uniform Title: Suite d'Orchestra, op. 22. Petit Mari, Petite Femme; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6566-9, undated; 31142040612841; 66623 (Box 99, Folder 1254)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: Petite Suite d'Orchestre Uniform Title: Petite suite d'orchestre Publisher information: Paris (France): A. Durand and Fils (E. Delanchy [printer]) Plate Number: D.S. and Cie 2942, undated; 31142040614474; 66622 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Composer: Bizet, Georges Title: Petite Suite d'Orchestre Uniform Title: Petite suite d'orchestre Publisher information: Paris (France): A. Durand and Fils Plate Number: D.S. and Cie. 2943, undated; 31142040614474; 66621 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Composer: Blake, Charles D. Title: Wanderings in Dreamland Uniform Title: Wanderings in Dreamland Publisher information: New York: White-Smith Publishing Co. Plate Number: 6932-9, undated; 31142040612908; 66620 (Box 105, Folder 1445)
  - Composer: Blanc, Louis Title: Boisterous Spirits. Polka Uniform Title: Boisterous Spirits; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5636-17, undated; 31142040612940; 66619 (Box 109, Folder 1554)
  - Composer: Bland, James A. Title: Carry Me Back to Old Virginny Uniform Title: Carry Me Back to Old Virginny Publisher information: Boston: The Boston Music Co. Plate Number: B.M.Co. 9055-6, undated; 31142040613450; 66618 (Box 151, Folder 2207)
  - Composer: Bleyle, Karl Title: Sieges-Ouverture, Op. 21 Uniform Title: Sieges-Ouverture, op. 21 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.2248/49., undated; 31142040614474; 66617 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Composer: Bliss, Paul Title: A Plainsman's Song Uniform Title: Plainsman's Song Publisher information: New York: The John Church Company Plate Number: 15832-4, undated; 31142040613492; 66616 (Box 147, Folder 2101)
  - Composer: Blon, Franz von Title: Lenz und Liebe. Waltz Uniform Title: Lenz und Liebe; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5249-23, undated; 31142040612940; 66615 (Box 109, Folder 1555)
  - Composer: Blon, Franz von Title: Mein Ideal. Waltz Uniform Title: Mein Ideal; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5173-26, undated; 31142040612957; 66614 (Box 110, Folder 1583)
  - Composer: Blon, Franz von Title: Universal Peace (Heil Europe) Uniform Title: Universal Peace; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer, undated; 31142040612957; 66613 (Box 110, Folder 1565)
  - Composer: Blon, Franz von Title: Vision (Traumbild) Uniform Title: Vision; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5791-20, undated; 31142040612577; 66612 (Box 72, Folder 930)
  - Composer: Blon, Franz von Title: Whispering Flowers (Blumengefluster) Uniform Title: Whispering Flowers; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5380-36, undated; 31142040612965; 66611 (Box 111, Folder 1598)
  - Composer: Blon, Franz von Title: Whispering Flowers (Blumengefluster) Uniform Title: Whispering Flowers; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5380-49, undated; 31142040612577; 66610 (Box 72, Folder 928)
  - Composer: Blon, Franz von Title: Whisperings of Love (Liebesgefluster) Uniform Title: Whisperings of Love; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6510-38, undated; 31142040612569; 66609 (Box 71, Folder 923)
  - Composer: Bloomfield, F. D. Title: The Peacemaker Uniform Title: Peacemaker; arr. Publisher information: Buffalo: J. L. Tindale, undated; 31142040612874; 66608 (Box 102, Folder 1350)
  - Composer: Blume, Hermann Title: Sehnsucht Uniform Title: Sehnsucht Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Hermann Blume (Dr. Rokotnitz [printer]) Plate Number: W 56, undated; 31142040613260; 66607 (Box 170, Folder 3025)
  - Composer: Blumner, Martin Title: Selig sind die Todten Uniform Title: Selig sind die Todten Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote and G. Bock Plate Number: 12969 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613260; 66606 (Box 170, Folder 2992)
  - Composer: Boccalari, E. Title: Souvenir of the Ball Uniform Title: Souvenir of the Ball Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 12215-23, undated; 31142040614474; 66605 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Composer: Boekelman, Bernardus Title: Ballabile Uniform Title: Ballabile, Op. 3; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bern. Boekelman (Oscar Brandstetter, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: B.B.5, undated; 31142040614466; 66604 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Composer: Boergermann, P. H. Title: Greeting Uniform Title: Greeting, undated; 31142040613344; 66603 (Box 162, Folder 2696)
  - Composer: Bohm, Carl Title: Birthday Festival Music Uniform Title: Geburtstag-Musik; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6019-47, undated; 31142040614474; 66602 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Composer: Bohm, Carl Title: Csikos et Bohemienne Uniform Title: Csikos et Bohemienne; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 21048-40, undated; 31142040614474; 66601 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Composer: Bohm, Carl Title: Kusshandchen (Love's Greeting). Mazurka Uniform Title: Kusshandchen. Mazurka Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 14403, undated; 31142040612882; 66600 (Box 103, Folder 1378)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: Die weisse Dame Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Jul. Weiss Plate Number: J.W.267., undated; 31142040614466; 66599 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche. Ouverture Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Publisher information: London (Great Britain): E. Donajowski (E. Donajowski, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: D.7264, undated; 31142040614466; 66598 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche. Overture Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 15833-88, undated; 31142040614466; 66597 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche. Overture Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Publisher information: Boston: W. H. Cundy Plate Number: 242-37(vl 1) 944-27 (vla, cor, drums, undated; 31142040614466; 66596 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: Offenbach a/M (Germany): Johann Andre Plate Number: ANDRE 12851, undated; 31142040614466; 66595 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: La Dame Blanche Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 4381, undated; 31142040614466; 66594 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: Overtura Uniform Title: Dame blanche. Ouverture Plate Number: 5539, undated; 31142040614466; 66593 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Composer: Boieldieu, Francois Adrien Title: The Calif of Bagdad. Overture Uniform Title: Calif of Bagdad. Overture; arr. Publisher information: New York: J. Schott's Plate Number: 254-44, undated; 31142040613104; 66592 (Box 125, Folder 1814)
  - Composer: Borel-Clerc, Ch. Title: La Sorella Uniform Title: Sorella Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick and Co., undated; 31142040612874; 66591 (Box 102, Folder 1357)
  - Composer: Borodin, Aleksandr Porfir'evich Title: Ballet Music (Polovetzian Dance) from the Opera Prince Igor, Part 2 Uniform Title: Prince Igor. Polovetsian Dances. Part 2 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 29405, undated; 31142040614466; 66590 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Composer: Borodin, Aleksandr Porfir'evich Title: Ballet Music (Polovetzian Dances) from the Opera Prince Igor, Part 1 Uniform Title: Prince Igor. Polovetsian Dances. Part 1 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 29403, undated; 31142040614466; 66589 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Composer: Bortnyans'ky [Bortniansky], Dmytro Stepanovych [Bortnyansky, Dmitry Stepanovich] Title: Ich bete an die Macht der Liebe Uniform Title: Ich bete an die Macht der Liebe, undated; 31142040613336; 66588 (Box 163, Folder 2715)
  - Composer: Bossi, Marco Enrico Title: Hochzeits-Marsch. Marcia Nuziale fur Orgel. Op. 110, No. 4 Uniform Title: Marcia Nuziale fur Orgel. Op. 110, No. 4; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 2373 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614458; 66587 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Composer: Bossi, Marco Enrico Title: Hochzeits-Marsch. Marcia Nuziale. Op. 110, No. 4 Uniform Title: Wedding March Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 2374 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614458; 66586 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Composer: Boustet, Ed. Title: Reve Apres le Bal Uniform Title: Reve Apres le Bal Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1593-28, undated; 31142040612486; 66585 (Box 63, Folder 809)
  - Composer: Bovy-Lysberg [Lysberg], Charles Samuel Title: La Fontaine Uniform Title: Fontaine Publisher information: New York: Spear and Dehnhoff Engraver: Cosack and Co., Buffalo, NY, undated; 31142040612858; 66584 (Box 100, Folder 1290)
  - Composer: Bowers, Fred V. Title: Sorrow Uniform Title: Sorrow Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein and Von Tilzer (Teller, Sons and Dorner, New York [printer]), undated; 31142040612874; 66583 (Box 102, Folder 1354)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: If You Were Lost to Me from The Vanderbilt Cup Uniform Title: Vanderbilt Cup. If You Were Lost to Me Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick and Co., undated; 31142040612916; 66582 (Box 106, Folder 1486)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: My House-Boat Beau from The Vanderbilt Cup Uniform Title: Vanderbilt Cup. My House-Boat Beau Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick and Co., undated; 31142040612882; 66581 (Box 103, Folder 1376)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: Somewhere in the World from The Vanderbilt Cup Uniform Title: Vanderbilt Cup. Somewhere in the World Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick and Co., undated; 31142040612874; 66580 (Box 102, Folder 1366)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: The Little Chauffeur from The Vanderbilt Cup Uniform Title: Vanderbilt Cup. The Little Chauffeur Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick and Co., undated; 31142040612874; 66579 (Box 102, Folder 1365)
  - Composer: Bowers, Robert Hood Title: The Red Rose. Selection Uniform Title: Red Rose. Selection; arr. Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick and Co., undated; 31142040614466; 66578 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Composer: Bowman, Euday L. Title: 12th Street Rag Uniform Title: 12th Street Rag; arr. Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein and Co. Inc., undated; 31142040613518; 66577 (Box 145, Folder 2029)
  - Composer: Bowman, Euday Louis Title: 12th Street Rag Uniform Title: 12th Street Rag Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein and Co. Inc., undated; 31142040613377; 66576 (Box 159, Folder 2571)
  - Composer: Braga, Gaetano Title: La Serenata Uniform Title: Serenata; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 7529, undated; 31142040612916; 66575 (Box 106, Folder 1493)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Academic Festival Overture, Op. 80 Uniform Title: Akademische Festouverture Publisher information: New York: Hampton Publications Plate Number: HOL-10, undated; 31142040614466; 66574 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Academic Festival Overture Uniform Title: Akademische Festouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22963-94, undated; 31142040614466; 66573 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Deutsches Requiem Uniform Title: Deutsches Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 593, undated; 31142040612742; 66572 (Box 89, Folder 1118)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Deutsches Requiem Uniform Title: Deutsches Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 594, undated; 31142040612742; 66571 (Box 89, Folder 1119)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Deutsches Requiem Uniform Title: Deutsches Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 595, undated; 31142040612742; 66570 (Box 89, Folder 1117)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Four Duets for Contralto and Baritone Uniform Title: Four Duets for Contralto and Baritone Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Augener and Co. Plate Number: A and Co. 5063, undated; 31142040612650; 66569 (Box 80, Folder 1033)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Klarinetten Quintett Uniform Title: Quintet, clarinet, violins, viola, violoncello, op. 115, B minor Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 9711, undated; 31142040613104; 66568 (Box 125, Folder 1817)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Liebeslieder Walzer Uniform Title: Liebeslieder Walzer, op. 52 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 7025, undated; 31142040613328; 66567 (Box 164, Folder 2781)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Rhapsodie Uniform Title: Rhapsodie, op. 53 Plate Number: 10626, undated; 31142040613278; 66566 (Box 169, Folder 2970)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Rhapsodie Uniform Title: Rhapsodie, op. 53 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 7036, undated; 31142040613278; 66565 (Box 169, Folder 2969)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Rhapsodie Uniform Title: Rhapsodies, alto, men's voices, orchestra, op. 53 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 7034 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613112; 66564 (Box 126, Folder 1824)
  - Composer: Brahms, Johannes Title: Rhapsodie Uniform Title: Rhapsodies, alto, men's voices, orchestra, op. 53 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 7037 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613112; 66563 (Box 126, Folder 1825)